<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="BtnNewGame">New game</string>
    <string name="labelPlayerChoice">Choose the players</string>
    <string name="addPlayer_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="btnContinue">Continue</string>
    <string name="pointsToWinTitle">Number of points to win</string>
    <string name="labelStoryTellerChoice">Who is the Storyteller ?</string>
    <string name="everyoneFoundTitle">Did everyone find the right card ?</string>
    <string name="everyoneFoundYesLabel">YES</string>
    <string name="everyoneFoundNoLabel">NO</string>
    <string name="endTurnTitle">End of turn !</string>
    <string name="whoDidFindLabel">Who found the right card ?</string>
    <string name="turnNumberPrefix">Turn n°</string>
    <string name="nextPlayer">Next player</string>
    <string name="EndGameButtonText">End of the game</string>
    <string name="notEnoughPlayers">You need at least 3 players to play Dixit !</string>
    <string name="wonTheGame">"won the game !"</string>
    <string name="duplicatedName">Please name players differently :)</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="playerName">Player Name</string>
    <string name="addPlayerButton">Add</string>
    <string name="emptyPlayer">Player name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="playerAlreadyExists">Player already exists</string>
    <string name="scoresEvolution">Scores recap</string>
    <string name="statsTitle">Statistics</string>
    <string name="playernameheader">Nom</string>
    <string name="nbgamesheader">Games played</string>
    <string name="nbwinsheader">Games won</string>
    <string name="winPercentageHeader">% Wins</string>
    <string name="enterANumberOfPointsToWin">Please provide a number in the box :)</string>
    <string name="BtnStats">Stats</string>
    <string name="whitespace"> </string>
    <string name="howToPlay">How to play ?</string>
    <string name="rules"><b><u>What you need to play :</u></b>  Dixit cards, and players &#128521; \n
        \n
        <b><u>How to play :</u></b>\n \n
            \t• Select the players in the app, then choose the number of points to win.\n
            \t• Give five cards to each player.\n
            \t• For the first turn, the first player that has an idea is the storyteller.\n
            \t• Choose his name in the app.\n
            \t• The storyteller chooses a card in his hand and says a (or some) word(s) in relation to this card, he puts the card in the middle (hidden).\n
            \t• Each player then selects a card in his hand matching what the storyteller said and puts it in the middle.\n
            \t• When every player has selected a card, the storyteller collects them all and shuffles them. Then he puts them on the table (artwork visible).\n
            \t• Players now need to find the card of the storyteller, everyone should keep quiet in order to not influence others.\n
            \t• When a player has made his choice, he raises his finger, meaning his decision is made.\n
            \t• When all the fingers are raised, the storytelles counts down from 3 to 1, and then everyone points at his elected card.\n
            \t• In the app, enter the choice of every player.\n
            \t• Scores are automatically updated using these rules :\n
                    \t\t• If no-one or everyone has found, the storyteller has 0 points and the players have 2 points.\n
                    \t\t• If at least one player has found the card of the storyteller, the storyteller and the players who found have 3 points.\n
                    \t\t• 1 additional point is granted at a player for each people who has voted for his card.\n
            \t• Then, the turn is over, and the players are sorted according to their scores.\n
            \t• When a turn is over, the new storyteller is the player at the left of the former storyteller, everyone draws a new card and a new turn begins.\n
            \t• The winner is the first player to reach the number of points to win, in case of draw, the game continues.\n
        &#127881; &#127881; Have fun !! &#127881; &#127881; \n
        \n
        <i>P.S.: Thanks for downloading the app, don\'t forget to rate it and post some update suggestions in the Play Store ;)</i>
    </string>
</resources>
